Jhal Hello
hello friends I am Vishal and you are
watching our channel Swasth Sort
Badhiya in this video we will see the
complete process of dismantling of these tracks dental
in movie short if you
want to see its full video then go to our channel
or I will put it in the backyard of Speed ​​OK ji
in 1962 and if you watch
such videos of accidents
of parents or want to improve difference related to
or want to do face
choda gaadi ghee lesson time work
then definitely ask in the comment below
we will definitely answer it if you
are new to the channel then please subscribe to our channel so
that
you can get immediate notification so that you keep getting updated from us
and whenever you drive you have to
wear helmet and follow traffic rules so that
you can do it
and thank you for watching the video thank you
Jai Hind